Когда…
When…
А-а…
Ah…
Я искал тебя, заглядывал во все магазины
I searched for you, peering into every shop.
Прилавки хранили твой запах тёплого смеха и сухого вина
The counters held your scent of warm laughter and dry wine.
Подозревал в твоей краже всех, включая кассиров
I suspected everyone of stealing you, including the cashiers.
Они ведь тоже могли смотреть в твои стеклянно-пустые глаза
After all, they too could have looked into your glassy, empty eyes.
Я, обезумев, бросаюсь за каждым прохожим
I, gone mad, rush after every passerby
Чьи волосы цвета ржи
whose hair is the color of rye.
А тонкие запястья лишь слегка на твои похожи
And slender wrists are only slightly like yours.
Через пару дней, из трещин в потолке
After a couple of days, from cracks in the ceiling,
Составляю твои черты
I piece together your features.
Я искал тебя в каждой чёртовой очереди
I searched for you in every damn queue.
Где ты?
Where are you?
Когда время придёт, мы окажемся рядом
When the time comes, we will be together.
Не торопись, всё своим чередом
Don't rush; everything in its own time.
Тебе так далеко до заката
You are so far from sunset.
А я здесь полежу
And I will lie here.
Я тебя подожду
I will wait for you.
Я тебя дождусь
I will wait until you come.
Тебя дождусь
I'll wait until you come.
Когда это случилось, мне почему-то стало полегче
When it happened, for some reason I felt a little better.
Теперь мне не нужно ждать зимы
Now I do not need to wait for winter;
Она тут со мной
it is here with me.
А ты поздней осенью ищешь меня не там
And you, in late autumn, search for me in the wrong place.
По первому снегу идёшь по пятам
Through the first snow, you walk in my footsteps.
Не иди, стой, постой
Don't go; stop, wait.
Я сам тебя найду
I myself will find you
Когда время придёт
when the time comes.
Ты ляжешь вместе со мной?
Will you lie down together with me?
Я лягу вместе с тобой
I will lie down together with you.
Время придёт, мы окажемся рядом
The time will come; we will be together.
Не торопись, всё своим чередом
Don't rush; everything in its own time.
Тебе так далеко до заката
You are so far from sunset.
А я здесь полежу
And I will lie here.
Я тебя подожду
I will wait for you.
Я тебя дождусь
I will wait until you come.
Я тебя подожду
I will wait for you.
Тебя дождусь
I'll wait until you come.
Дождусь тебя
Где ты?
Where are you?